salutations welcome to the cottage fairy
today i will be making my own paper and
wanted to give you some insight into
the process it's quite simple
slow and meditative a beautiful way to
reuse paper scraps and consequently
reduce waste
[Music]
learning new crafts is very important to
me
i'm always trying out new ideas and
projects
working with your hands in order to
create something either useful
or beautiful is always so exciting
in the case of paper making i create
something that
is both
[Music]
traditional and nature-based crafts hold
a special place in my heart
in a world where fast fashion is
mainstream where you often only find
factory made products on store shelves
becoming an artisan changes you as a
consumer
it gives you insight into the process of
creating forming a story behind the end
result
i find my home feels far more meaningful
filled with things that i have created
myself
[Music]
learning new crafts brings me joy
because it teaches me patience
acquiring a skill takes time and
whatever you create
is made more meaningful because you
created it
[Music]
do
with each attempt i will become more
skilled the results more sophisticated
and my efforts rewarded but all this
takes patience
in the meantime i enjoy the excitement
of learning
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
closed captioning
sometimes my projects don't work out
like i imagined
there is something that goes straight
into the compost but that's why i
started this channel
to embrace the process of creating no
matter the result
i wanted to share my passion for making
beauty or trying to make beauty in
alignment with nature
be it through art or crafts cooking or
simply living my dream
[Music]
i am an artist and consequently like to
make artistic videos through lovely
images of my home
i want to send out peaceful thoughts and
hope
and faith that anything is possible and
that life can be
if you choose full of joy and meaning
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
after a long day i find no greater gift
of care
you can give yourself than a homemade
meal
i struggle to have thoughtful sit-down
meals
and using my own vegetables and herbs
motivates me to slow down
focus on my senses and truly appreciate
the gift of an abundant
[Music]
harvest
[Applause]
you